{
    "id": "4038f360b41647ffa9ccb5564e64f39a",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The dog ……………. the horse.",
            "description": "Bit is the past tense of bite.",
            "answers": [
                "bit",
                "bite",
                "bitten"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32118e9e1737445db153776caf2eadaf"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… cats like cold water.",
            "description": "Few is similar to hardly any. A few is somewhat similar to some or several.",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "A few",
                "The few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b0465d9fc1b4cdabdab82e035f72c74"
        },
        {
            "question": "He died in the village ……………………. he was born.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "where",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c2145056d602476b803e8b45321e7829"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog that ………………… does not bark.",
            "description": "The verb in the relative clause should agree with the antecedent of the relative pronoun in number and person.",
            "answers": [
                "bites",
                "bite",
                "biting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6d63639a331341469c04842ebbfacfab"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is nothing else ………………….. pride.",
            "description": "Else should be followed by but.",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "than",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "77bcab41865b428e9e2a1aad0b912d19"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………. intelligent.",
            "description": "We do not normally use ‘so’ to indicate a higher degree of something. Very is used with that meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "68b5491abb6e4c89be8816c34efe1179"
        },
        {
            "question": "He went only ……………… far.",
            "description": "That cannot be used as an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "too",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1f0e440cc81143f6b4e327b865862b9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ………………… tired that he could barely stand.",
            "description": "That cannot be used as an adverb. Too cannot be used before a that-clause.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd6dc6d80f7c49049d1c71e224fd9475"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………… exhausted to work.",
            "description": "Too means more than enough.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6bd10efb2de24f55b57bbdd26529a5c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The flowers smell ………………….....",
            "description": "Smell is a copular verb. We use adjectives to modify copular verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "sweet",
                "sweetly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8f4fd48557a5406cb919ce7ba50a71bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ………………………… cold.",
            "description": "Bitter is an adjective. We cannot use an adjective to modify another adjective. We need an adverb. Bitterly is an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "bitter",
                "bitterly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "687067f64b2b450893dabb19a5259a4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never seen a more ……………………….. football match.",
            "description": "The past participle is used to say how people feel. The present participle is used to describe the people or things that cause the feelings.",
            "answers": [
                "excited",
                "exciting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "874db1b3a0cf4d3dacc1d6a361321f8b"
        }
    ]
}